# Prince Issar

Zaventem, Flemish Region, Belgium



princeissar@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/princeissar

### Summary

ICT: I'm highly motivated young professionals in full stack development.

Also done PSM-1 Scrum Master training.

I'm Flexible, highly motivated and determined.

HOTEL INDUSTRY: I am a professional hotelier with several years of work experience in the Receptionist Duties and management and I always try to provide the best customer service.

REAL ESTATE: I have acquired during my experience negotiations skills, how to building trustful business relationships and successfully secured the deals.

### **Experience**



### Microsoft 365 Power Platform Consultant

Hub.Co

Aug 2023 - Present (2 months)

### Business Analyst

delaware BeLux

Sep 2022 - May 2023 (9 months)

### Analyst developer IT

**SNDQ** 

Dec 2021 - Mar 2022 (4 months)

Property management solution(PaaS) using Low code (WEM)

# Project Manager Intern

Qollabi

Oct 2021 - Nov 2021 (2 months)

BRM solution

### Student - Junior Web developer

BeCode.org

Apr 2021 - Oct 2021 (7 months)

#### Shift leader

The President Brussels Hotel

### # Réceptionniste

Holiday Inn Brussels Airport Sep 2018 - Mar 2019 (7 months)

# Réceptionniste

Aspria Group Feb 2018 - Sep 2018 (8 months)

### Front Desk Réceptionniste

Hotel Metropole Brussels Apr 2017 - Jan 2018 (10 months) 5 star and the oldest hotel in Brussels.

### **Night Manager**

**Aloft Hotels** Nov 2012 - Apr 2014 (1 year 6 months)

### Real Estate Agent

Bhal & son Real estate Jan 2009 - Jun 2012 (3 years 6 months)

### **Education**



Professional Scrum Master, Project Management Oct 2021 - Oct 2021

## BeCode

Diploma of Education, Information Technology Apr 2021 - Oct 2021

### **Licenses & Certifications**

php - BeCode.org

# Professional Certified Scrum (PSM - 1) - Scrum.org

GitHub - BeCode.org

# Chrome Web Developer Tools

- Learn How to Learn OpenClassrooms 3134828677
- Mendix Rapid development
  43269
- Microsoft Certified: Power Platform Fundamentals Microsoft Issued Jan 2023 Expires Jan 2024
- Microsoft Certified: Power Platform App Maker Associate Microsoft Issued Jan 2023 Expires Jan 2024

### **Skills**

Technical Requirements • Methodology • Communication • Database Management System (DBMS) • Scrum • Front-End Development • Teamwork • NoSQL • HTML • Microsoft Dynamics